Register of the William H. Rehnquist papers
Hoover Institution Archives
William H. Rehnquist papers
1947-2005
2009C15
Hoover Institution Archives
571 manuscript boxes, 318 cubic foot boxes, 2 card file boxes, 2 oversize boxes (548.0 linear feet)
Documents the Supreme Court terms of William H. Rehnquist, associate justice from 1972 to 1986 and chief justice from 1986 to 2005. Materials include court case files, administrative files, conference files, correspondence, speeches and writings, book manuscripts, invitations, and other materials. Also includes Rehnquist's law school notebooks from his time at Stanford Law School in 1951 and 1952.
Rehnquist, William H., 1924-2005
Access
Boxes 322-331 and 359-893 closed. The remainder of the collection is open for research.
U.S. Supreme Court case files and related materials for the Supreme Court's October Terms 1975-2005 in boxes 359-830 shall remain closed during the lifetime of any member of the Supreme Court who served with William H. Rehnquist.
Impeachment files in boxes 322-331, and 893 are closed. Video depositions within the impeachment files in box 330 are closed until 2048 in accordance with Senate Resolution 474.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2008.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
Born on October 1, 1924 in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, William Hubbs Rehnquist served in the Army Air Corps in North Africa during World War II. Once the war ended he attended Stanford University, where he received a B.A. in political science. He then earned master's degrees from both Stanford and Harvard, before completing Stanford Law School in 1952. After completing law school, Rehnquist served as a clerk to Supreme Court Justice Robert H. Jackson.
Rehnquist married Natalie Cornell, whom he had met at Stanford during his law school years, on August 29, 1953. They had three children. Rehnquist practiced law in Phoenix, Arizona, from 1953 to 1969, becoming active in Republican politics during this time. Joining President Richard Nixon's administration in 1969 as head of the office of legal counsel in the Justice Department, in October 1971, President Nixon nominated Rehnquist to be an associate justice on the Supreme Court.
Rehnquist served as an associate justice until 1986, when President Ronald Reagan nominated him to replace retiring Chief Justice Warren Earl Burger. Rehnquist was the sixteenth Chief Justice, serving more than 30 years on the Supreme Court. He has the distinction of serving as the second Chief Justice in U.S. history to preside over an impeachment trial of a president, in 1999. A notable decision in Rehnquist's tenure as chief justice was Bush v. Gore (2000), which effectively decided the 2000 presidential election for George W. Bush by stopping the recount of contested ballots in Florida.
As Chief Justice, Rehnquist stated that his goal was to be remembered as a good administrator. Known for his strong leadership, conservative interpretation of the Constitution, and decisions enhancing the power of the states in the federal system, Rehnquist retained his conservative perspective throughout his tenure on the Court. Ill with thyroid cancer, Rehnquist served as Chief Justice as long as his health permitted. He died on September 3, 2005, in Arlington, Virginia, and is buried in Arlington National Cemetery.
Resources:
"William Rehnquist" in American Decades 1990-1999. Tandy McConnell, ed. Gale Group, 2001 in Biography Resource Center. Farmington Hills, Mich.: Gale, 2008. Accessed 3 November 2008. http://galenet.galegroup.com/servlet/BioRC
"William Rehnquist," The Scribner Encyclopedia of American Lives. Ed. Arnold Markoe, Karen Markoe, and Kenneth T. Jackson. Vol. 7: 2003-2005. Detroit: Charles Scribner's Sons, 2007 in Biography Resource Center. Farmington Hills, Mich.: Gale, 2008. Accessed 3 November 2008. http://galenet.galegroup.com/servlet/BioRC
Scope and Content of Collection
The William H. Rehnquist papers mainly document Rehnquist's time as a justice of the United States Supreme Court, from 1972 to 1986, then as chief justice from 1986 to 2005. A small amount of material also documents Rehnquist's studies at Stanford Law School in 1951 and 1952.
The Stanford Law School Notebooks and Journal contain Rehnquist's class notes, with another volume documenting his accounts and personal journal entries with non-continuously dated portions from 1947 to 1965.
Documentation on the U.S. Supreme Court includes Administrative Files, which document the functional management of the court. Materials include stays, opinions, subject files, correspondence, conference and order lists, and vote sheets. Some administrative files contain collected information on subjects such as abortion cases or capital cases.
U.S. Supreme Court Case Files contain official printed drafts of each case opinion circulated among the justices. Some files also contain concise correspondence, memoranda, and other materials regarding the case. In many instances there are multiple cases within one file. Materials are organized by the court term, or October term, in which the case was heard.
The U.S. Supreme Court Administrative and Case Files from 1972 through 1974, and Rehnquist's Stanford Law School Notebooks and Journal were opened November 17, 2008. Printed Opinions and Syllabi, Correspondence, and materials on Rehnquist's books, as well as additional materials including speeches, writings, notebooks, and other documents, opened in August 2009.
United States. Supreme Court; Law--United States.
- Stanford Law School Notebooks and Journal, 1947-1965
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes a journal with non-continuous writings dating from 1947-1948 and 1965, and notebooks from Rehnquist's time at Stanford Law School.
  - Journal, 1947-1965 (Box 1)
    Labeled Record Book, item contains non-continually dated accounts and journal entries along with documentation of a trip to California in 1948.
  - Stanford Law School notebooks, 1951-1952 (Boxes 1-3)
    Six notebooks include class notes for Administrative Law, Admiralty, Wills, Conflicts, Corporations, Future Interests, Constitutional Law, Equity Notes, Taxation and Conveyances, 1952.
- U.S. Supreme Court Administrative Files, 1969-1974
  Files contain administrative documentation on cases, including stays, opinions, subject files, correspondence, conference and order lists, and vote sheets. Arranged chronologically.
  - 1969-1972 (Box 3)
    Case background material labeled "Personal - to keep."
  - 1971
    - Capital cases files for 1971 term: 69-5003, William Henry Furman v. State of Georgia; 69-5030, Lucious Jackson, Jr. v. State of Georgia; 69-5031, Elmer Branch v. State of Texas; 69-5027, Ernest James Aikens, Jr. v. State of California, (4 folders) (Boxes 3-4)
      "Circulated drafts of the opinion, joint memoranda, conference memoranda, per curiam, and concise correspondence between the justices
    - Cases held for decision on Moose Lodge, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Stay applications, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Seventh Circuit and other applications, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Hearing lists and summaries, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Opinions, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Decisions, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Assignment lists, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Judicial conference of U.S. proceedings, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence file, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Personal correspondence with Justices, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Lists: addresses and attendees at meetings (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1971 (Box 5)
  - 1972
    - Cases held pending final disposition, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Seventh Circuit applications, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Seventh Circuit orders by William Rehnquist, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Stay applications memos, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Stay in Lyndon B. Johnson v. Stevenson, 1948, reviewed, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Other chambers applications memos, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Memos by Justice Frankfurter (Box 5)
    - Responses requested, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Personal correspondence with Justices, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Visitors, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Park service, 1972 (Box 5)
  - 1973
    - Term information - cases granted for 1973 term (Box 5)
    - Chronological file, 1973-1974 term cases (Box 5)
    - Conference memos regarding cases (Box 5)
    - Summaries of cases to be argued (Box 5)
    - Cases coming down (Box 6)
    - Cases held for memos (Box 6)
    - Stay applications memos, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Stay applications, memos from other Chambers (Box 6)
    - Stay applications regarding Vietnam bombing, summer, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Seventh Circuit applications, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Seventh Circuit orders by Rehnquist, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Circulatories (Box 6)
    - Alphabetical correspondence regarding cases
      - 1972-1973
        - A-I (Box 7)
        - J-P (Box 7)
        - Q-Z (Box 7)
      - 1973-1974
        - A-I (Box 7)
        - J-S (Box 8)
        - T-Z (Box 8)
    - Personal correspondence with Justices, 1973 (Box 8)
    - Clerks general correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
    - Abortion cases (Box 8)
    - Reappointment cases (Box 8)
    - Religious school cases (Box 8)
    - Nixon, Richard file, (2 folders) (Boxes 8-9)
    - Obscenity, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Obscenity cases - unargued (Box 9)
      Includes correspondence.
  - 1974
    - Stay applications, memos from other Chambers (Box 9)
    - Personal correspondence with Justices (Box 9)
  - Order and conference lists
    - Conference lists, 1972
      - January 7 (Box 9)
      - January 14 (Box 9)
      - January 21 (Box 9)
      - February 18 (Box 9)
      - February 25 (Box 10)
      - March 3 (Box 10)
      - March 6 (Box 10)
      - March 17 (Box 10)
      - March 24 (Box 10)
      - March 31 (Box 10)
      - April 14 (Box 10)
      - April 21 (Box 10)
      - May 12 (Box 10)
      - May 19 (Box 10)
      - May 29 (Box 10)
      - June 5 (Box 10)
      - June 9 (Box 10)
      - June 15 (Box 10)
      - June 22 (Box 10)
      - June 26 (Box 10)
      - October 2 (Box 10)
      - October 13 (Box 11)
      - October 20 (Box 11)
      - November 3 (Box 11)
      - November 10 (Box 11)
      - November 17 (Box 11)
      - December 1 (Box 11)
      - December 8 (Box 11)
      - December 15 (Box 11)
    - Order lists, 1972
      The absence of a case number means the file refers to multiple cases
      - January 10 (Box 11)
      - January 17 (Box 11)
      - 71-221. Peggy J. Connor v. John Bell Williams, Governor of Mississippi, January 24 (Box 11)
      - 70-5075. Jack Boyd v. A. L. Dutton, Warden, February 22 (Box 11)
      - 71-486. Dennis Gary Monger v. State of Florida, February 28 (Box 11)
      - March 3 (Box 11)
      - 71-5552. Fred A. Cruz v. George J. Beto, Director, Texas Department of Corrections, March 20 (Box 11)
      - 70-251. Lionel Adolph Joseph v. United States, March 20 (Box 11)
      - 71-5560. William Isaac Miller v. State of Oregon, April 3 (Box 11)
      - 71-5580. Rudy Gonzales v. George J. Beto, Director, Texas Department of Corrections, April 17 (Box 11)
      - April 24 (Box 11)
      - 71-6274. Donald Bruce McGarva v. United States, May 10 (Box 11)
      - 71-5910. Eddie David Cox v. United States, May 15 (Box 11)
      - 31 Original State of Utah v. United States, May 22 (Box 11)
      - 71-6393. David Greene v. United States, June 6 (Box 11)
      - 71-784. Dorothy Taylor v. John J. McKeithen, Governor of Louisiana, June 12 (Box 11)
      - 71-1219. Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference v. Federal Power Commission; 71-1220. City of New York v. Federal Power Commission; 71-1221. Sierra Club and Its Atlantic Chapter v. Federal Power Commission, June 19 (Box 11)
      - 71-1044. David A. Rosenfeld v. New Jersey, June 26 (Box 11)
      - 71-5440. John S. Stewart v. Massachusetts, June 29 (Box 11)
      - A-23 and A-24 - Demo. Delegates Lawrence O'Brien v. Willie Brown, Thomas E. Keane v. National Democratic Party, July 7 (Box 11)
      - October 10 (Box 12)
      - 71-1386. Ohio AFL-CIO, The United Autoworkers of Ohio v. Insurance Rating Board, October 16 (Box 12)
      - 57 Original State of Illinois v. State of Michigan, October 24 (Box 12)
      - 71-6743. Willie Horace Bryant v. North Carolina, November 6 (Box 12)
      - 71-5780. Celestino Rivas v. Robert C. Cozens, Director, California Department of Motor Vehicles, November 13 (Box 12)
      - November 20 (Box 12)
      - 71-6647. Alfred David Webb v. State of Texas, December 4 (Box 12)
      - 72-376. One Lot Emerald Cut Stones and One Ring v. United States, December 11 (Box 12)
      - 72-521. Irish Northern Aid Committee v. Attorney General of the United States, December 18 (Box 12)
    - Conference lists, 1973
      - January 5 (Box 12)
      - January 12 (Box 12)
      - January 19 (Box 12)
      - February 16 (Box 12)
      - February 23 (Box 12)
      - March 2 (Box 12)
      - March 16 (Box 12)
      - March 23 (Box 12)
      - March 30 (Box 12)
      - April 13 (Box 12)
      - April 20 (Box 12)
      - May 4 (Box 12)
      - May 11 (Box 12)
      - May 17 (Box 12)
      - May 25 (Box 12)
      - June 1 (Box 12)
      - June 8 (Box 12)
      - June 15 (Box 12)
      - June 22 (Box 12)
      - October 1 (Box 13)
      - October 12 (Box 13)
      - October 19 (Box 13)
      - November 2 (Box 13)
      - November 9 (Box 13)
      - November 16 (Box 13)
      - November 30 (Box 13)
      - December 7 (Box 13)
      - December 14 (Box 13)
    - Order lists, 1973
      - Original State of Nebraska v. State of Iowa, January 8, 17 (Box 13)
      - 72-603. Elliot L. Richardson, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Deborah Morris, January 15 (Box 13)
      - 72-438. United States v. Edward G. Chandler and Esther F. Born, January 22 (Box 13)
      - February 20 (Box 13)
      - 72-686. Department of Motor Vehicles of the State of California v. Federico Rios, a Minor, February 26 (Box 13)
      - 72-5431. Raymond N. Ortwein and Gwendolyn Faubion v. Herbert M. Schwab, March 5 (Box 13)
      - 72-794. Barbara Susan Papish v. The Board of Curators of the University of Missouri, March 19 (Box 13)
      - 72-864. William B. Camp, Comptroller of the Currency of the United States v. F. W. Pitts, March 26 (Box 13)
      - 71-364 and 71-373. 71-364. John S. Mahan, Secretary, State Board of Elections v. Henry E. Howell, Jr.; 71-373. City of Virginia Beach v. Henry E. Howell, April 2 (Box 13)
      - 72-805. United States v. Alphonse T. Indrelunas, April 16 (Box 13)
      - 72-1130. Ivo H. Denham and Geraldine A. Denham dba The Denham Company v. National Labor Relations Board, April 23 (Box 13)
      - 2-6011. Frank X. Gaca v. United States, May 7 (Box 13)
      - May 14 (Box 13)
      - 72-6075. Jerome T. Bland v. United States, May 21 (Box 13)
      - May 29 (Box 13)
      - 72-1164. Deborah A. Northcross v. Board of Education of the Memphis City Schools, June 4 (Box 13)
      - 72-1310. Sam Dean v. The Gadsden Times Publishing Corporation, June 11 (Box 13)
      - 72-1350. Robert Keelan Meisel, Jr. and Barbara Jean Fitch v. United States, June 18 (Box 14)
      - 71-1190. H. Dean Summers v. Pete T. Cenarrusa, June 25 (Box 14)
      - October 9 (Box 14)
      - 72-552. Robert Satiacum v. State of Washington, October 15 (Box 14)
      - 72-1296. Robert O. Carlson v. State of Minnesota, October 23 (Box 14)
      - 72-1366. Edward Norwell v. City of Cincinnati, Ohio, November 5 (Box 14)
      - November 12 (Box 14)
      - 73-5256. Melvin Lee v. United States, November 19 (Box 14)
      - 73-241. Chicago Mercantile Exchange v. Darryl B. Deaktor, December 3 (Box 14)
      - 73-459. Norman New Rider, By His Mother and Next Friend, Wilma Williams v. Board of Education of Independent School District 1, Pawnee County, Oklahoma, December 10 (Box 14)
      - December 17 (Box 14)
    - Conference lists, 1974
      - January 4 (Box 14)
      - January 11 (Box 14)
      - January 18 (Box 14)
      - February 15 (Box 14)
      - February 22 (Box 14)
      - March 1 (Box 14)
      - March 15 (Box 14)
      - March 22 (Box 14)
      - March 29 (Box 14)
      - April 12 (Box 14)
      - April 19 (Box 14)
      - April 26 (Box 14)
      - May 10 (Box 14)
      - May 24 (Box 15)
      - May 31 (Box 15)
      - June 7 (Box 15)
      - June 14 (Box 15)
      - June 25 (Box 15)
      - July 23 (Box 15)
    - Order lists, 1974
      - 73-200. Roy Splawn v. State of California, January 7 (Box 15)
      - 73-731. Francis Snider v. All State Administrators, Inc., January 21 (Box 15)
      - 73-568. Wilbur Schmidt, Director of Wisconsin Department of Health and Social Services v. Alberta Lessard, January 14 (Box 15)
      - Phillips Petroleum Company v. Texaco, Inc., February 19 (Box 15)
      - Francis J. Moran v. C. A. Neff, Superintendent, Field Unit # 21, February 20 (Box 15)
      - 74-428. United States v. Norbert Nisan Kahan, February 25 (Box 15)
      - 4 March (Box 15)
      - 18 March (Box 15)
      - 73-5925. Terry Dean Eaton v. City of Tulsa; 73-1169. Flaherty and Whipple v. Arkansas, March 25 (Box 15)
      - 73-996. George Erckman v. United States, April 1 (Box 15)
      - 73-1131. James S. Mahon, Trustee, and C.I.T. Corporation v. Curtis R. Stowers, April 15 (Box 15)
      - 22 April (Box 15)
      - 29 April (Box 15)
      - 73-5842. Eugene Robert Ciuzio v. United States, May 13 (Box 15)
      - 73-6230. Peter Brescia v. State of New Jersey, May 28 (Box 15)
      - 50 Original, State of Vermont v. State of New York, June 3 (Box 15)
      - 73-6271. John Michaels, Anonymous Juvenile v. State of Arizona, June 10 (Box 15)
      - 73-899. Joseph P. Moody v. Albemarle Paper Company and Williams v. Albemarle City Board of Education, June 17 (Box 15)
      - 24 June (Box 15)
      - 8 July (Box 15)
      - A-1265. Missouri Portland Cement Co. v. Cargill, Inc., July 25 (Box 15)
  - Vote sheets, argued cases, 1970-1974
    - 1970-1974 (Box 16)
      Statistical sheets of court
    - 1972 (Box 16)
    - 1973 (Box 16)
    - 1974, (2 folders) (Box 16)
- U.S. Supreme Court Case Files, 1972-1974
  Case files generally contain printed official drafts of each case, with minimal correspondence, notes, and memoranda regarding the case. In many instances, there are multiple cases in a file. In the container list, a "Found in case" notation means that the case number is within another case file. A "See also" notation means that there is another relevant or similar case. Arranged chronologically by October term, then by docket number.
  - 1971 October Term (January 1972-September 1972) and 1972 October Term (October 1972-September 1973), 1972-1973
    - Bob Bullock, Secretary of State of Texas v. Dan Weiser Et Al (Box-folder 17: A-760)
    - State of Nebraska v. State of Iowa (Box-folder 17: 17 Original)
    - State of Ohio v. State of Kentucky (Box-folder 17: 27 Original)
    - State of Michigan v. State of Ohio (Box-folder 17: 30 Original)
    - State of Texas v. State of Louisiana (Box-folder 17: 36 Original)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. State of New York (Box-folder 17: 40 Original)
    - State of Washington v. General Motors Corporation (Box-folder 17: 45 Original)
    - State of Illinois v. City of Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Box-folder 17: 49 Original)
    - State of Vermont v. State of New York (Box-folder 17: 50 Original)
    - United States v. States of Nevada and California (Box-folder 17: 59 Original)
    - Donald Felix Schneble v. State of Florida (Box-folder 17: 68-5009)
    - Joseph Arthur Zicarelli v. The New Jersey State Commission of Investigation (Box-folder 17: 69-4)
    - Lymann A. Moore v. State of Illinois (Box-folder 17: 69-5001)
    - Frank Johnson v. Louisiana (Box-folder 18: 69-5035)
      Note
      See also case 69-5046
    - Robert Apodaca, Harry Morgan Cooper, Jr., and James Arnold Madden v. Oregon (Box-folder 18: 69-5046)
      See also case 69-5035
    - United States v. 12 200-Ft. Reels of Super 8mm Film (Box-folder 18: 70-2)
    - Albert Sarno and Chris Cardi v. Illinois Crime Investigating Commission (Box-folder 18: 70-7)
    - Thomas E. Eisenstadt, Sheriff of Suffolk County, Massachusetts v. William R. Baird (Box-folder 18: 70-17)
    - Jane Roe v. Henry Wade (Box-folder 18: 70-18)
      Includes official printed drafts of the opinion along with minimal correspondence. Additional information on the Roe v. Wade case may be found in the Administrative Files from 1972 in the Abortion cases file, which includes the draft opinions and correspondence between justices before the decision, as well as correspondence received by Rehnquist after the decision.
    - Socialist Labor Party v. Gilligan, Governor of Ohio (Box-folder 18: 70-21)
    - Millard Gooding v. Johnny C. Wilson (Box-folder 18: 70-26)
    - United States v. Edna Generes, Wife of, and Allen H. Generes (Box-folder 19: 70-28)
    - John Giglio v. United States (Box-folder 19: 70-29)
    - Charles R. Perry v. Robert P. Sindermann (Box-folder 19: 70-36)
    - United States v. The Pullman Company. Found in case 70-5033 (Box-folder 19: 70-37)
    - Federal Power Commission v. Florida Power & Light Company (Box-folder 19: 70-38)
    - Mary Doe v. Arthur K. Bolton, as Attorney General of the State of Georgia (Box-folder 19: 70-40)
    - United States v. Daniel B. Brewster (Box-folder 19: 70-45)
    - Florence Diffenderfer and Nishan Paul v. Central Baptist Church of Miami, Florida, Inc. (Box-folder 19: 70-47)
    - United States v. Mississippi Chemical Corporation (Box-folder 19: 70-52)
    - Board of Regents of the University of Texas System v. New Left Education Project (Box-folder 19: 70-55)
    - United States v. Earl Caldwell (Box-folder 19: 70-57)
      See also cases 79-85 and 70-94
    - Securities and Exchange Commission v. Medical Committee for Human Rights (Box-folder 19: 70-61)
    - United States v. George Joseph Orito (Box-folder 19: 70-69)
    - Marvin Miller v. State of California (Box-folder 20: 70-73)
    - Pipefitters Local Union 562 v. United States (Box-folder 20: 70-74)
    - Moose Lodge 107 v. K. Leroy Irvis (Box-folder 20: 70-75)
    - Reliance Electric Company v. Emerson Electric Company (Box-folder 21: 70-79)
    - Paul M Branzburg v. John P. Hayes, Judge (Box-folder 21: 70-85)
      Contains printed drafts of the opinion circulated among the justices, concurring opinions, brief correspondence between the justices, and agreements to dissent correspondence. The file also includes information on case 70-94, regarding Paul Pappas, and case 70-57, United States v. Earl Caldwell. See also cases 70-57 and 70-94
    - United States v. Forrest S. Tucker (Box-folder 21: 70-86)
    - Police Department of the City of Chicago v. Earl D. Mosley (Box-folder 21: 70-87)
    - S&E Contractors, Inc. v. United States (Box-folder 21: 70-88)
    - Joseph Parisi v. Philip B. Davidson (Box-folder 21: 70-91)
    - California Motor Transport Co. v. Trucking Unlimited (Box-folder 21: 70-92)
    - In the Matter of Paul Pappas (Box-folder 21: 70-94)
      Found in cases 70-57 and 70-85
    - Evansville-Vanderburgh Airport Authority District v. Delta Airlines, Inc. (Box-folder 21: 70-99)
      See also case 70-212
    - State of Wisconsin v. Jonas Yoder (Box-folder 21: 70-110)
    - Ford Motor Company v. United States (Box-folder 22: 70-113)